{
    "id": "b57219432e124aac8ecf2075d513734b",
    "title": "Adjective Or Adverb",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He runs ………………………..",
            "description": "Fast can be an adjective and an adverb. There is no need for the word fastly.",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03195c3356ad48f4bc729c53fcdbbba7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can speak English ………………………….. than French.",
            "description": "We need a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "more fluent",
                "more fluently",
                "fluently"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cfb80bd0d2db478fa09b7a468d714299"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pretty girl smiled …………………………. at the guests.",
            "description": "Here we use the adverb warmly to modify the verb smiled.",
            "answers": [
                "warm",
                "warmly",
                "more warmly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "30746086816d4b5eab1d5c486d3d2b2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looked ………………………….. than ever before.",
            "description": "Happier is the comparative form of happy.",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "more happy",
                "happier"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d33511e68b5d46ec88bc71140139ca3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you write more …………………………?",
            "description": "Legible is an adjective. We need the adverb legibly to modify the verb write.",
            "answers": [
                "legible",
                "legibly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1b13b3654823496a9fa9a2341f22d628"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her performance was the ………………………. of all.",
            "description": "Worst is the superlative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worser",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d69ddff4542b4c85ac822f2d1e721be2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They handled the situation quite ………………………..",
            "description": "We need the adverb sensibly to modify the verb handled. More cannot be used with quite.",
            "answers": [
                "sensible",
                "sensibly",
                "more sensibly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4d2fd0d0a2e41ab8ae749692caacf95"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………………….. interest in politics.",
            "description": "Little is the positive form of the adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d936a51192d43908051cb9be947eda1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn …………………………. money than my mother.",
            "description": "We use less with uncountable nouns and few with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3b3fc2ebe5f446089ed7f3257f7441b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "This essay has …………………………. mistakes than the other.",
            "description": "We use less with uncountable nouns and few/fewer with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "lesser",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ed8e9f3098146b384b165f103879c65"
        },
        {
            "question": "She works ……………………….. than her husband.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "more hard"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47b74512fb0140669b94e0facd344465"
        },
        {
            "question": "He works …………………………… to support his family.",
            "description": "Hard can be an adjective and an adverb. Hardly is similar to scarcely. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e279fd8956f44f180bc52dfa311fd32"
        }
    ]
}